sharewarejunction.com 2009-06-20

# Liquid Mirror Enterprises - Software Books Web Sites Services eBooks

**Please remember us next time you're looking for great software. Better yet,click here to bookmark us now so more than 40,000 free downloads are just one click away!**

## PRIVACY POLICY

At Liquid Mirror Enterprises we strive to protect your privacy and rights. We have set forth this statement to explain the information we collect from you, how we use that information, and your legal rights regarding that information.Who has access to my information?The information you provide is controlled by Liquid Mirror Enterprises of Laguna Hills, CA ("Data Controller"). What information do we collect and how do we use it?
* When you place an order, we need to know your email address, delivery and billing address, password and company name if you are a business. You may optionally provide your fax, mobile number and website address which helps us contact you urgently if there is a problem with your order.
* We may provide your telephone number to a courier should they need to contact you regarding your delivery.
* If you choose to pay by credit or debit card, you will be asked to provide your card details on a secure form using 128-bit encryption. These are held securely by Wells Fargo. We do not get to see your card details. All credit card refunds are made through Wells Fargo who ensure the correct card is credited.
* When you choose to contact us through a web form, we need your name, email address, and telephone number. This information is used to contact you if we need to respond to your question.
* We personalise your shopping experience by recommending products through the use of cookies. A cookie is used to store your profile against which recommendations are made, and to remember your language preferences.
* We use a cookie to store your basket contents during your visit.
* We may from time to time analyse your personal information and profile to enable us to review, develop and improve our products and services which we offer and to enable us to provide you with relevant information through our marketing programme. If you do not wish to receive information regarding new products and services, company news, or changes to this website, you may opt-out by emailing info@liquidmirror.com.
* We may use your personal information in the prevention and detection of fraud.
* We may use your information to administer any prize draws or competitions you may enter.How do we protect your information?When you place an order with us, we take all reasonable steps to ensure your personal information is stored safely on our servers. Only employees of the Data Controller who handle the technical management of our website can access your information. Only the Data Controller will process your information for completion of your order. We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information you provide to prevent unauthorised access. Our procedures mean we may occasionally request proof of identity before disclosing information to you. We cannot however guarantee the security of any data you disclose to us online.Do we disclose your information to third parties?We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties. If we choose to do so in the future, you will be notified by email of our intentions, and have the right to be removed prior to the disclosure.

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. These may include packaging companies to fulfil orders, couriers to make deliveries, The US Postal Service to send post, and marketing companies to inform you of our new products and services. These companies will have access to your personal information, but may not use it for any other purpose.

Your consent and rightsBy using our website you consent to the collection and use of this information by Liquid Mirror Enterprises. Changes to this privacy policy will be posted to this page so that you are kept informed of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Your commentsWe welcome comments on our privacy policy. Please email your questions and comments from the contact page. Alternatively you can write to us at the following address

> The Sharware Junction Network  
>  Liquid Mirror Enterprises  
>  24338 El Toro Rd. Ste E-414  
>  Laguna Hills, CA 92637 USA 

Copyright © 2009 [Liquid Mirror Enterprises](http://www.liquidmirror.com/). All rights reserved. Reproduction in whole or in part in any form or medium without express written permission of Liquid Mirror Enterprises is strictly prohibited. Use of this site subject to Terms and Conditions. Privacy Policy
